Applied and Decorative Arts Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- M etalwork (Box 55)
  - United States [Slide boxes 65-73] (Box 65)
    - Goldwork (Box 65)
      - Fueter, David (Box 65)
      - Johnson, Samuel (Box 65)
      - Meyer, Meyer (Box 66)
      - Revere, Paul (Box 66)
      - Richardson, Joseph, Sr. (Box 66)
      - Richardson, Joseph, Jr. (Box 66)
      - Soumaine, Simeon (Box 66)
      - Van der Spiegel, Jacobus (Box 66)
      - Van Voorhis, D. (Box 66)
    - Silverwork (Box 66)
      - Anonymous artists (Box 66)
      - Known artists, A-Z (Box 66)
        - A (Box 66)
        - B (Box 67)
          - Boelen, Jacob (Box 67)
          - Burt, Benjamin (Box 67)
          - Burt, John (Box 67)
        - C (Box 67)
          - Coney John (Box 67–68)
            - Cups (Box 68)
            - Plates (Box 68)
            - Tankards (Box 68)
        - D (Box 68)
          - Dixwell, John (Box 68)
          - Dummer, J. (Box 68)
            - Cups (Box 68)
            - Spoons (Box 68)
        - E (Box 68)
          - Edwards, J. (Box 68)
        - F (Box 69)
          - Faris, William (Box 69)
        - G (Box 69)
        - H-J (Box 69)
          - Hull, John (Box 69)
          - Hull and Sandelen (Box 69)
          - Hurd, Jacob (Box 69)
        - K (Box 70)
          - Kierstede, C (Box 70)
        - L (Box 70)
          - Le Roux, B. (Box 70)
          - Le Roux, C. (Box 70)
        - M (Box 70)
          - Meyers, M (Box 70)
        - N (Box 70)
          - Nys, Johannes (Box 70)
        - O (Box 70)
        - P-Q (Box 71)
        - R (Box 71)
          - Revere, Paul (Box 71)
            - Bowls (Box 71)
            - Sugar bowls (Box 71)
            - Tea Pots/Kettles (Box 71)
          - Richardson, Joseph and Nathaniel (Box 72)
            - Tankards (Box 72)
            - Tea Pots (Box 72)
        - S (Box 72)
          - Sanderson (Box 72)
        - T-U (Box 72)
        - V (Box 72)
          - Van der Burgh, Cornelius (Box 72)
          - Van der Spiegel, Jacobus (Box 73)
          - Van Dyck, P. (Box 73)
          - Vincent, W. (Box 73)
        - W-Z (Box 73)
          - Winslow, E (Box 73)
            - Sugar bowls (Box 73)
          - Wynkoop, B. (Box 73)
          - Wynkoop, C. (Box 73)
- Mosaics (Box 74)
  - Early Medieval-Renaissance (Box 74)
    - Albenga (Box 74)
    - Aquileia (Box 74)
    - Capua Vetere (Box 74)
    - Casale Monferrato (Box 74)
    - Cefalu (Box 74)
    - Civita Castelana (Box 74)
    - Cologne (Box 74)
    - Constantinople (Box 74)
      - Imperial Palace (Box 74)
      - Hagia Irene (Box 74)
      - Hagia Sophia (Box 74)
    - Cremona (Box 74)
    - Damascus (Box 74)
    - Daphni (Box 75)
    - Ephesus (Box 75)
    - Florence (Box 75)
      - Baptistry (Box 75)
    - Germigny-des-Pres (Box 75)
    - Hosias Loukas (Box 75)
    - Ivrea (Box 75)
    - Kiev (Box 75)
    - Latran (Box 75)
    - Lucca (Box 75)
    - Milan (Box 75)
    - Monreale (Box 75–76)
    - Murano (Box 76)
    - Naples (Box 76)
    - Otranto (Box 76)
    - Palermo (Box 76)
      - Cappella Palatina (Box 76)
      - La Martorano (Box 76)
      - La Ziza (Box 76)
    - Piacenza (Box 76)
    - Ravello (Box 76)
    - Ravenna (Box 76)
      - Archepiscopal Palace (Box 76)
      - Arian Baptistry (Box 76)
      - S. Apollinaire in Classe (Box 76)
      - S. Appollinaire Nuovo (Box 77)
      - S. Vitale (Box 77)
      - Tomb of Galla Placidia (Box 77)
      - Tomb of Theodo (Box 77)
    - Rome (Box 77)
      - Oratory of Pope John VII (Box 77)
      - S. Agnese (Box 77)
      - S. Cecilia (Box 77)
      - SS. Cosmos and Damian (Box 77)
      - S. Croce in Gerusalemme (Box 78)
      - S. Giovanni in Laterano (Box 78)
      - S. Maria in Domnica (Box 78)
      - S. Maria Maggiore (Box 78)
      - S. Maria in Trastevere (Box 78)
      - S. Paolo f.l.m. (Box 78)
      - S. Peter's (Box 78)
      - S. Prassure (Box 78)
      - S. Prudenziana (Box 78)
      - S. Sabina (Box 78)
    - St. Denis (Box 79)
    - Salonika (Box 79)
      - Hagia Georgios (Box 79)
      - Holy Apostles (Box 79)
      - S. Demetrios (Box 79)
    - Torcello (Box 79)
    - Venice (Box 79)
      - S. Marco (Box 79)
    - Vercelli (Box 79)
- Musical Instruments (Box 80)
  - Flanders (Box 80)
  - France (Box 80)
  - United States (Box 80)
- Numismatics (Box 80)
  - Mesopotamia (Box 80)
  - Early Medieval (Box 80)
  - Britain (Box 80)
  - Italy (Box 80)
  - Spain (Box 80)
  - United States (Box 80)
    - Hull and Sanderson (Box 80)
  - Asia Minor (Anatolia) (Box 80)
- Rugs (Box 80)
  - The Caucasus (Box 80)
  - Central Asia (Box 80)
  - Persia (Box 80)
  - Spain (Box 81)
  - United States (Box 81)
- Seals (Box 81)
  - Mesopotamia (Box 81)
- Stage Design (Box 81)
  - Austria (Box 81)
    - Hakart, Hans (Box 81)
  - Britain (Box 81)
    - Jones, Inigo (Box 81)
  - France (Box 81)
    - Leger, Fernand (Box 81)
    - Picabia, Francis (Box 81)
  - Germany (Box 81)
    - Schlemmer, Oskar (Box 81)
    - Schmidt, Karl (Box 81)
  - Italy (Box 81)
    - Bazzani (Box 81)
  - Russia (Box 81)
    - Eisenstein, Sergei (Box 82)
    - Exter, Alexandra (Box 82)
    - Lissitsky, El (Box 82)
    - Malevich, K (Box 82)
    - Pevsner, A (Box 82)
    - Shestakov, V (Box 82)
    - Stepanova, V (Box 82)
    - Tatlin, V. (Box 82)
    - Vasnetsov, V.M. (Box 82)
    - Vesnin, Alexander (Box 82)
  - Spain (Box 82)
  - United States (Box 82)
    - Geddes, Norman Bel (Box 82)
    - Jones, Robert (Box 82)
- Stained Glass (Box 82)
  - Technique (Box 82)
  - Britain (Box 82)
    - Canterbury (Box 82)
  - Flanders (Box 82)
  - France (Box 82)
    - Amiens (Box 82)
    - Anger (Box 82)
    - Auxerre (Box 82)
    - Beauvais (Box 82)
    - Bourges (Box 82)
    - Brou (Box 83)
    - Chalais-sur-Marne (Box 83)
    - Champigny (Box 83)
    - Chartres (Box 83)
      - Ambulatory (Box 83)
        - La Belle Verriere (Box 83)
        - Charlemagne Window (Box 83)
        - S. James Window (Box 83)
        - S. Thomas Window (Box 83)
      - Apse (Box 83)
      - Nave (Box 83)
      - West Facade (Box 83)
        - Center lancet (Box 83)
        - South lancet (Box 83)
      - North Transept (Box 83)
      - South Transept (Box 83)
        - St. Denis Window (Box 83)
    - Gassicourt (Box 84)
    - Guengat (Box 84)
    - Le Ferte Milon (Box 84)
    - Le Mans (Box 84)
    - Lyon (Box 84)
    - Metz (Box 84)
    - Montmorency (Box 84)
    - Obazine (Box 84)
    - Paris (Box 84)
    - Quimper (Box 84)
    - Reims (Box 84)
    - St. Remi (Box 84)
    - Rouen (Box 84)
    - S. Denis (Box 84)
      - Allegories of St. Paul (Box 84)
      - Childhood of Christ (Box 84)
      - Ezechiel (Box 84)
      - Griffin (Box 84)
      - Life of Moses (Box 84)
      - Tree of Jesse (Box 84)
    - S. Julien du Sault (Box 84)
    - Sens (Box 84)
    - Strassbourg (Box 84)
    - Vendome (Box 84)
    - 20th century (Box 85)
      - Leger, Fernand (Box 85)
      - Matisse, Henri (Box 85)
  - Germany (Box 85)
  - Holland (Box 85)
  - Italy (Box 85)
  - Switzerland (Box 85)
    - Lausanne Cathedral (Box 85)
  - United States (Box 85)
- Tapestry (Box 85)
  - Britain (Box 85)
  - Flanders (Box 85)
    - 15th century (Box 85)
      - Van der Weyden, Rogier (Box 85)
    - 16th century (Box 85)
      - Coxcie, M. (Box 85)
      - Orley, Bernard (Box 86)
      - Rome, Jan van (Box 86)
      - Vermeyen, Cornelisz (Box 86)
    - 18th century (Box 86)
  - France (Box 86)
    - Bayeux Tapestry (Box 86)
      - 1-10 (Box 86)
      - 11-20 (Box 86)
      - 21-30 (Box 86)
      - 31-40 (Box 86)
      - 41-50 (Box 86)
      - 51-60 (Box 86)
    - 14th century (Box 87)
      - Angers Apocalypse (Box 87)
      - Nine Heroes (Box 87)
    - 15th century (Box 87)
      - Lady and the Unicorn (Box 87)
    - 16th century (Box 87)
      - Life of the Virgin (Box 87)
    - 17th century (Box 87)
    - 18th century (Box 87)
    - 20th century (Box 87)
      - Gromaire, Marcel (Box 87)
      - Ranson, Paul (Box 88)
      - Simon, Lucien (Box 88)
  - Germany (Box 88)
  - Italy (Box 88)
    - Raphael (Box 88)
  - Norway (Box 88)
  - Spain (Box 88)
  - Spain (Box 88)
  - Switzerland (Box 88)
  - United States (Box 88)
- Textiles (Box 88)
  - Coptic (Box 88)
  - Near East (Box 88)
  - Early Medieval (Box 88)
  - Britain (Box 89)
    - S. Cuthbert's Coffin (Box 89)
    - 16th-18th centuries (Box 89)
    - 19th-20th centuries (Box 89)
      - Burne-Jones, Edward (Box 89)
      - Morris, William (Box 89)
  - France (Box 89)
  - Germany (Box 89)
    - Obrist, H. (Box 89)
  - Greece (Box 89)
  - India (Box 89)
  - Italy (Box 89)
  - Spain (Box 90)
  - Sweden (Box 90)
  - Switzerland (Box 90)
  - Latin America (Box 90)
  - United States (Box 90)
    - Rugs and carpets (Box 90)
    - Albers, Anni (Box 90)
    - Stehl silks (Box 90)
- Wallpaper (Box 91)
  - Britain (Box 91)
  - France (Box 91)
  - Germany (Box 91)
  - United States (Box 91)
- Wood carving (Box 91)
  - Belgium (Box 91)
  - Britain (Box 91)
    - Gibbons, Grinling (Box 91)
  - France (Box 91)
  - Germany (Box 91)
  - Italy (Box 91)
  - Spain (Box 91)